Guide to the George A. Romero Archival Collection, 1962-2017 SC.2019.03
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Production Materials, circa 1962-2008; II.
  - Produced Works, circa 1962-2008; 1.
    - The Little World of Humongo Dongo [Le Petit Monde d'Humongo Dongo], 1993-1994; 25.
      A children's book about fantastical creatures trying to coexist despite their differences while also learning about their impact on the ecology and environment of their planet. Originally published in Belgium in a French translation as Le Petit Monde d'Humongo Dongo.
      - The Little World of Humongo Dongo contracts and correspondence, 1993-1994 (Box 69, Folder 6)
    - Toe Tags [Toe Tags Featuring George A. Romero] [The Death of Death], 2003-2004; 26.
      A six-issue comic book series telling a new version of the zombie apocalypse in which a small group attempts to survive and understand the reasons why the dead have risen. Also known as Toe Tags Featuring George A. Romero and "The Death of Death." Published by DC Comics in 2004-2005. Written by George A. Romero and illustrated by Tommy Castillo.
      - Toe Tags contracts, correspondence, overview, and draft storylines, 2003-2004 (Box 69, Folder 7)
      - Toe Tags artwork sketches and final galleys, 2004-2005 (Box 69, Folder 8)
  - Unproduced Works, circa 1964-2006; 2.
    This subseries contains materials related to the development, production, financing, and distribution of unmade or incomplete film and television projects by George A. Romero. This includes correspondence (including some script revisions when included with correspondence), contracts, shooting schedules and shot lists, storyboards, fundraising materials, cast and crew lists, budget documents, and production binders.
    - Apartment Living, 1986-1992; 1.
      - Apartment Living production materials and correspondence, 1987-1992 (Box 69, Folder 9)
        Various materials related to the production of Apartment Living. Correspondence and contracts outline history of development including documents related to earlier authors of the story, Warren Hitte and Joseph Stillman. Also includes treatment and story notes, budgets, and title research reports.
    - The Assassination, 2001; 2.
      - The Assassination agreements, February - April 2001 (Box 69, Folder 10)
    - Before I Wake, 1992-1996; 3.
      - Before I Wake story notes, outlines, and correspondence, 1992-1993 (Box 69, Folder 11)
      - Before I Wake story notes, outlines, and correspondence, 1994 (Box 70, Folder 1)
      - Before I Wake story notes, outlines, and correspondence, 1995-1996 (Box 70, Folder 2)
      - Before I Wake legal correspondence and contracts, 1993-1995 (Box 70, Folder 3-4)
      - Before I Wake prospective location managers, November 15, 1994 (Box 70, Folder 5)
      - Before I Wake prospective directors of photography, December 1994 - February 1996 (Box 70, Folder 6)
      - Before I Wake proposed budget for Toronto shoot, August 29, 1994 (Box 70, Folder 7)
      - Before I Wake proposed budget for Pittsburgh and Los Angeles shoot, January 30, 1996 (Box 70, Folder 8)
      - Before I Wake proposed budget for Toronto and Pittsburgh shoot, February 1, 1996 (Box 70, Folder 9)
      - Before I Wake proposed budget for Pittsburgh shoot, February 2, 1996 (Box 70, Folder 10)
      - Before I Wake budget memos and correspondence, 1994-1996 (Box 70, Folder 11)
      - Before I Wake casting ideas and memos, 1994-1996 (Box 70, Folder 12)
      - Before I Wake set list, December 5, 1995 (Box 70, Folder 13)
      - Before I Wake contact lists, January 19, 1996 (Box 70, Folder 14)
      - Before I Wake pre-production schedules and maps, January - February 1996 (Box 70, Folder 15)
      - Before I Wake shooting schedules, December 1995 - February 1996 (Box 70, Folder 16)
      - Before I Wake storyboards, circa 1995-96 (Box 71, Folder 1)
        Two sets of storyboards drawn by P. Tatopoulos.
      - Before I Wake VFX proposals, breakdowns, budgets, and tests, January - March 1996 (Box 71, Folder 2)
        Proposals, breakdowns, budgets, tests, and correspondence from a variety of VFX firms. Also includes printed ghost effects tests.
    - Bell Witch, circa 1998; 4.
      - Bell Witch research and overview for production with Bravo, circa 1998 (Box 71, Folder 3)
    - Black Mariah, 1993; 5.
      - Black Mariah contract, rights, and legal correspondence, May - December 1993 (Box 71, Folder 4)
      - Black Mariah novel to film strategy, story notes, treatment revisions, and correspondence, May - July 1993 (Box 71, Folder 5)
        Correspondence with revisions and story notes.
      - Black Mariah story notes, treatment revisions, and correspondence, August - November 1993 (Box 71, Folder 6)
    - Carnivore, 1999; 6.
      - Carnivore correspondence, May 6 - 12, 1999 (Box 71, Folder 7)
        Includes letter to the Wachowskis.
    - Cartoon, 1992-1993; 7.
      - Cartoon correspondence, pitch, and VFX proposal, 1992-1993 (Box 71, Folder 8)
    - Chain Letter, 1997-1999; 8.
      - Chain Letter correspondence and agreement, 1997-1999 (Box 71, Folder 9)
    - The Collaboration, 1989; 9.
      - The Collaboration script notes, August 7, 1989 (Box 71, Folder 10)
    - Copperhead Conquers the Warhawks [Mongrel: The Legend of Copperhead], 1983; 10.
      - Copperhead Conquers the Warhawks title straw poll and associated correspondence, August 15 - September 2, 1983 (Box 71, Folder 11)
      - Copperhead Conquers the Warhawks character, costume, and set sketches with memo, 1983 (Box 71, Folder 12)
    - Death Hunters, 1999; 11.
      - Death Hunters correspondence, February 16, 1999 (Box 71, Folder 13)
    - The Death of Death, 1999; 12.
      - Copyright letter for "The Death of Death (Chapter 1)", December 23, 1999 (Box 71, Folder 14)
    - Divine Spirit, undated; 13.
      - Divine Spirit budget sheets (4 copies), undated (Box 71, Folder 15)
    - The Footage [Bigfoot], 1976; 14.
      - The Footage [Bigfoot] production materials, April - June 1976 (Box 71, Folder 16)
        Various production materials including: letter regarding potential casting of Franco Harris, personnel lists, proposed budgets, equipment needs, sketches for bigfoot, photographs of makeup tests, and news clippings about bigfoot.
    - Germs, 1997; 15.
      - Letter regarding proposed animated show for WB Network, August 26, 1997 (Box 71, Folder 17)
    - The Girl Who Loved Tom Gordon, circa 2004; 16.
      - Letter from George A. Romero to Stephen King about The Girl Who Loved Tom Gordon, undated (Box 71, Folder 18)
      - The Girl Who Loved Tom Gordon draft budgets, May 23, 2004 (Box 71, Folder 19)
    - The Golem, 1996; 17.
      - Letter from Chris Romero regarding potential production, August 30, 1996 (Box 71, Folder 20)
    - Goosebumps, 1995-1996; 18.
      - Goosebumps correspondence and agreement, 1995-1996 (Box 71, Folder 21)
        Includes correspondence, agreements, and expenses.
    - Hell, circa 1996; 19.
      - Letter to MGM regarding draft revisions and potential future of project, circa 1996 (Box 72, Folder 1)
        Dated December 8, 1976, but likely 1996.
    - Hell Hotel, 1992-1996; 20.
      - Letter to New Line Television confirming pitch period to explore interest in development of series, September 3, 1992 (Box 72, Folder 2)
      - Correspondence and contracts with Walt Disney Television to pursue development of series, 1995-1996 (Box 72, Folder 3)
    - Hoffman: Through the Mansions of the Moon, 1985; 21.
      - Hoffman costume, set, and production design materials, March 22-23, 1985 (Box 72, Folder 4)
        Correspondence, notes, and breakdowns for costumes, sets, and SFX from costume and production designers Barbara and Cletus Anderson
      - Hoffman correspondence, agreements, and copyright materials, June - December, 1985 (Box 72, Folder 5)
        Correpondence and fillings for copyright, agreements, and letter from John Harrison regarding music composition.
    - The Ill, 1999-2000; 22.
      - The Ill correspondence and agreement with P-Kino films, 1999-2000 (Box 72, Folder 6)
    - It, 1988-1989; 23.
      - It correspondence & script notes, 1988-1989 (Box 72, Folder 7)
        Correspondence on scripts between George A. Romero and Lawrence (Larry) D. Cohen.
    - It Came from Within, 1997-1998; 24.
      - It Came from Within correspondence for project developed between Romero and Richard Matheson, 1997-1998 (Box 72, Folder 8)
    - King Bee, 1997; 25.
      - Letter confirming Romero attachment to proposed project, February 13, 1997 (Box 72, Folder 9)
    - The Legend of Sleepy Hollow, 1997-1998; 26.
      - The Legend of Sleepy Hollow production materials, 1997-1998 (Box 72, Folder 10)
        Includes proposal for IMAX 3-D film and correspondence.
    - The Light at the End, 1985; 27.
      - The Light at the End correspondence and notes, September - November 1985 (Box 72, Folder 11)
        Correspondence, meeting notes, and a unattributed treatment for production of film adaptation of the 1986 novel The Light at the End by John Skipp and Craig Spector.
    - The Long Walk, 1987; 28.
      - Agreement to grant rights to Romero to adapt the 1979 novel The Long Walk by Stephen King (writing as Richard Bachman)., April 13, 1987 (Box 72, Folder 12)
    - Maledictus, 2004; 29.
      - Correspondence and agreement for potential project titled Maledictus, December 8, 2004 (Box 72, Folder 13)
    - Midnight Motel, 1999; 30.
      - Midnight Motel correspondence, April - May 1999 (Box 72, Folder 14)
        Correspondence and treatment/outline for a proposed television series by Tommy Lee Wallace which seeks to recruit different directors for each episode. Includes correspondence from Romero and John Carpenter expressing interest to join project.
    - Midnight Show, 1999; 31.
      - Letter from REZN8 Productions with shot list and FX notes as well as treatment of Midnight Show by Romero for reference., February 17, 1999 (Box 72, Folder 15)
    - Moonshadows, 1996-1998; 32.
      - Correspondence and agreement with 20th Century Fox for proposed project Moonshadows, 1996-1998 (Box 72, Folder 16)
    - The Mummy [1980s], 1986-1987; 33.
      - Copyright review, correspondence, and treatment for The Mummy and Return of the Mummy, 1986-1987 (Box 72, Folder 17)
    - Native Tongue, 1996; 35.
      - Correspondence on development of adaptation of the 1991 novel by Carl Hiaasen Native Tongue, April - June 1996 (Box 72, Folder 22)
    - Pet Sematary, 1984-1988; 36.
      - Pet Sematary correspondence, contracts, and meeting notes, 1984 (Box 72, Folder 23)
        Includes correspondence, contracts, notes, budgets.
      - Pet Sematary effects budget breakdown and memos, June - September 1985 (Box 73, Folder 1)
      - Pet Semetary storyboards and notes for scenes that will require VFX, August 9, 1985 (Box 73, Folder 2)
    - Phobophila [Bandit at Twelve O'Clock], 1993; 37.
      - Correspondence and overview for Penn and Teller TV Series called Phobophila, July 1993 (Box 73, Folder 6)
    - Quevira, 1998; 38.
      - Quevira correspondence and budget, May - November 1998 (Box 73, Folder 7)
    - The Raven, 1995-1998; 39.
      - The Raven correspondence and agreements, 1995-1996 (Box 73, Folder 8)
      - The Raven correspondence, 1998 (Box 73, Folder 9)
    - Red Eye, 1998-1999; 40.
      - Correspondence for potential project called Red Eye, 1998-1999 (Box 73, Folder 10)
    - Resident Evil, 1998; 41.
      - Resident Evil correspondence and agreement, 1998 (Box 73, Folder 11)
    - Shake Him Till He Rattles, 1996; 42.
      - Letter from Chris Romero regarding potential project titled Shake Him Till He Rattles, June 26, 1996 (Box 73, Folder 12)
    - Shoo-Be-Doo-Be Moon, 1978; 42.
      - Shoo-Be-Doo-Be Moon promotional folder with story synopsis by Rudolph J. Richie (9 copies), 1978 (Box 73, Folder 13)
    - Spirit Moves, 1993; 43.
      - Spirit Moves treatments, script notes, and correspondence, June - July 1993 (Box 73, Folder 14)
    - Stray, 1997; 44.
      - Contract with Spelling Television Inc. to develop series titled Stray, November 6, 1997 (Box 73, Folder 15)
    - Turn of the Screw, 1987-1988; 45.
      - Turn of the Screw budget and correspondence, 1987-1988 (Box 73, Folder 16)
    - Unholy Fire, 1991-1993; 46.
      - Legal correspondence, contract, option rights with New Line Cinema for Unholy Fire, 1992-1993 (Box 73, Folder 17)
      - Correspondence with Whitley Strieber on potential projects, 1992-1993 (Box 73, Folder 18)
      - Unholy Fire story/scene outlines and notes, 1992 (Box 73, Folder 20)
      - Unholy Fire correspondence, 1993 (Box 73, Folder 21)
      - Unholy Fire second draft-in-progress with correspondence from Whitley Streiber, May 18, 1993 (Box 73, Folder 22)
      - Unholy Fire Act 1 script notes, 1993 (Box 74, Folder 2)
    - Virtual City, circa 1993-1994; 47.
      - Outline, treatment, notes, and legal correspondence for potential project titled Virtual City, 1993-1994 (Box 74, Folder 4)
    - War of the Worlds, 1986-1992; 48.
      - War of the Worlds contracts, 1986-1992 (Box 74, Folder 5)
    - Whine of the Faun, circa 1964; 49.
      - Whine of the Faun promotional and fundraising booklet, circa 1964 (Box 74, Folder 6)
    - Zombisodes, April 2006; 50.
      - Zombisodes chronology and one-line schedule, April 16-17, 2006 (Box 74, Folder 7)
    - Untitled Projects, circa 1987-1999; 51.
      - "Untitled Romero Classic" agreement, February 13, 1987 (Box 74, Folder 8)
      - Loose sheet from unidentified New Line project, undated (Box 74, Folder 9)
      - "IMAX Horror Film Project" agreement and correspondence, 1999 (Box 74, Folder 10)
    - Multiple Projects, circa 1970-1993; 52.
      - Image 70 Productions: a motion picture investment binder, circa 1970 (Box 74, Folder 11)
        Proposal created by Latent Image, Inc. for potential investors detailing history of the company, projects, and their personnel (including George A. Romero). Also includes synopses and production budgets for two new proposed projects titled Something Evil and Cold Fear. Also include production photographs from Night of the Living Dead and There's Always Vanilla.
      - List of RGP projects with synopses, 1992-1993 (Box 74, Folder 12)
        Includes correspondence, development status, and synopses for Apartment Living, Big Lazarus, Cartoon, Hot-l Diablo, Jacaranda, The Most Deadly Game, The Mummy, The Scarecrow, Trolls, Unholy Fire, Whippersnapper.
- Publicity, 1962-2009; III.
  This series contains materials produced by outside parties about the works of George A. Romero, including reviews, interviews, and news items from newspapers and magazines, as well as festival programs and cinema calendars.
  - Press Clippings, 1962-2009; 1.
    This subseries contains materials produced by outside parties about the works of George A. Romero, including reviews, interviews, and news items from newspapers and magazines.
    - Press clippings, 1962-1968 (Box 75, Folder 1)
    - Press clippings, 1969 (Box 75, Folder 2)
    - Press clippings, 1970 (Box 75, Folder 3)
    - Press clippings, 1971 (Box 75, Folder 4)
    - Press clippings, 1972 (Box 75, Folder 5)
    - Press clippings, January-July 1973 (Box 75, Folder 6)
    - Press clippings, August-December 1973 (Box 75, Folder 7)
    - Press clippings, 1974 (Box 75, Folder 8)
    - Press clippings, 1975 (Box 75, Folder 9)
    - Press clippings, March 1976 (Box 75, Folder 10)
    - Press clippings, April 1976 (Box 75, Folder 11)
    - Press clippings, May 1976 (Box 75, Folder 12)
    - Press clippings, June 1976 (Box 75, Folder 13)
    - Press clippings, July 1976 (Box 75, Folder 14)
    - Press clippings, January-July 1977 (Box 75, Folder 15)
    - Press clippings, August-December 1977 (Box 75, Folder 16)
    - Press clippings: Martin album, 1977-1979 (Box 76, Folder 1)
    - Press clippings: Martin undated, circa 1977-1979 (Box 76, Folder 2)
    - Press clippings: Dawn of the Dead undated, circa 1978-1980 (Box 76, Folder 3)
    - Press clippings, January-April 1978 (Box 76, Folder 4)
    - Press clippings, May 1978 (Box 76, Folder 5)
    - Press clippings, June 1978 (Box 76, Folder 6)
    - Press clippings, July 1978 (Box 76, Folder 7)
    - Press clippings, August 1978 (Box 76, Folder 8)
    - Press clippings, September 1978 (Box 76, Folder 9)
    - Press clippings, October 1978 (Box 76, Folder 10)
    - Press clippings, November 1978 (Box 76, Folder 11)
    - Press clippings, December 1978 (Box 76, Folder 12)
    - Press clippings, January-February 1979 (Box 76, Folder 13)
    - Press clippings, March 1979 (Box 77, Folder 1)
    - Press clippings, April 1979 (Box 77, Folder 2)
    - Press clippings, May 1979 (Box 77, Folder 3)
    - Press clippings, June 1979 (Box 77, Folder 4)
    - Press clippings, July 1979 (Box 77, Folder 5)
    - Press clippings, August 1979 (Box 77, Folder 6)
    - Press clippings, October 1979 (Box 77, Folder 7)
    - Press clippings, November 1979 (Box 77, Folder 8)
    - Press clippings, December 1979 (Box 77, Folder 9)
    - Press clippings: Knightriders undated, circa 1980-1982 (Box 77, Folder 10)
    - Fangoria articles, circa 1980-1981 (Box 77, Folder 11)
    - Press clippings, January 1980 (Box 77, Folder 12)
    - Press clippings, February 1980 (Box 77, Folder 13)
    - Press clippings, Spring 1980 (Box 77, Folder 14)
      Includes The Amusement Park review by Tony Williams.
    - Press clippings, March 1980 (Box 77, Folder 15)
    - Press clippings, May 1980 (Box 77, Folder 16)
    - Press clippings, June 1980 (Box 78, Folder 1)
    - Press clippings, July 1980 (Box 78, Folder 2)
    - Press clippings, August 1980 (Box 78, Folder 3)
    - Press clippings, September 1980 (Box 78, Folder 4)
    - Press clippings, October-December 1980 (Box 78, Folder 5)
    - Press clippings, January 1981 (Box 78, Folder 6)
    - Press clippings, February 1981 (Box 78, Folder 7)
    - Press clippings, March 1981 (Box 78, Folder 8)
    - Press clippings, April 1981 (Box 78, Folder 9)
    - Press clippings, May 1981 (Box 78, Folder 10)
    - Press clippings, June 1981 (Box 78, Folder 11)
    - Press clippings, July 1981 (Box 78, Folder 12)
    - Press clippings, August 1981 (Box 78, Folder 13)
    - Press clippings, September 1981 (Box 78, Folder 14)
    - Press clippings, October 1981 (Box 78, Folder 15)
    - Press clippings, November 1981 (Box 78, Folder 16)
    - Press clippings, December 1981 (Box 78, Folder 17)
    - Press clippings, January 1982 (Box 79, Folder 1)
    - Press clippings, February 1982 (Box 79, Folder 2)
    - Press clippings, March 1982 (Box 79, Folder 3)
    - Press clippings, April 1982 (Box 79, Folder 4)
    - Press clippings, May 1982 (Box 79, Folder 5)
    - Press clippings, June 1982 (Box 79, Folder 6)
    - Press clippings, July 1982 (Box 79, Folder 7)
    - Press clippings, August 1982 (Box 79, Folder 8)
    - Press clippings, September 1982 (Box 79, Folder 9)
    - Press clippings, October 1982 (Box 79, Folder 10)
    - Press clippings, November 1982 (Box 79, Folder 11)
    - Press clippings, November 1982 (Box 80, Folder 1)
    - Press clippings, November 1982 (Box 80, Folder 2)
    - Press clippings: Creepshow undated, circa 1981-1983 (Box 80, Folder 3)
    - Press clippings, January 1983 (Box 80, Folder 4)
    - Press clippings, March 1983 (Box 80, Folder 5)
    - Press clippings, April 1983 (Box 80, Folder 6)
    - Press clippings, June 1983 (Box 80, Folder 7)
    - Press clippings, July 1983 (Box 80, Folder 8)
    - Press clippings, December 1983 (Box 80, Folder 9)
    - Press clippings, December 1984 (Box 80, Folder 10)
    - Press clippings, May-June 1985 (Box 80, Folder 11)
    - Press clippings, July-August 1985 (Box 80, Folder 12)
    - Press clippings, September-October 1985 (Box 80, Folder 13)
    - Press clippings, January-February 1986 (Box 80, Folder 14)
    - Press clippings, June-October 1986 (Box 80, Folder 15)
    - Press clippings, November 1986 (Box 80, Folder 16)
    - Press clippings: Monkey Shines undated, circa 1988-1989 (Box 80, Folder 17)
    - Press clippings, February 1988 (Box 80, Folder 18)
    - Press clippings, May 1988 (Box 80, Folder 19)
    - Press clippings, June 1988 (Box 80, Folder 20)
    - Press clippings, July 1988 (Box 81, Folder 1)
    - Press clippings, August 1988 (Box 81, Folder 2)
    - Press clippings, September 1988 (Box 81, Folder 3)
    - Press clippings, October 1988 (Box 81, Folder 4)
    - Press clippings, December 1988 (Box 81, Folder 5)
    - Press clippings, January 1989 (Box 81, Folder 6)
    - Press clippings, October 1990 (Box 81, Folder 7)
    - Press clippings, December 1990 (Box 81, Folder 8)
    - Press clippings, January 1991 (Box 81, Folder 9)
    - Press clippings, October 1991 (Box 81, Folder 10)
    - Press clippings, June 1992 (Box 81, Folder 11)
    - Press clippings, October 1992 (Box 81, Folder 12)
    - Press clippings, March 1993 (Box 81, Folder 13)
    - Press clippings, April 1993 (Box 81, Folder 14)
    - Press clippings, May 1993 (Box 81, Folder 15)
    - Press clippings, June 1993 (Box 81, Folder 16)
    - Press clippings, August 1993 (Box 81, Folder 17)
    - Press clippings, 1998 (Box 81, Folder 18)
    - Press clippings, 1999 (Box 81, Folder 19)
    - Press clippings, 2000 (Box 82, Folder 1)
    - Press clippings, 2001 (Box 82, Folder 2)
    - Press clippings, 2002 (Box 82, Folder 3)
    - Press clippings, 2003 (Box 82, Folder 4)
    - Press clippings, 2004 (Box 82, Folder 5)
    - Press clippings, May 2005 (Box 82, Folder 6)
    - Press clippings, June 2005 (Box 82, Folder 7)
    - Press clippings, July 2005 (Box 82, Folder 8)
    - Press clippings, August 2005 (Box 82, Folder 9)
    - Press clippings, June 2007 (Box 83, Folder 1)
    - Press clippings, September 2007 (Box 83, Folder 2)
    - Press clippings: French-language Diary of the Dead reviews, 2008 (Box 83, Folder 3)
      Bound notebook of reviews.
    - Press clippings, 2009 (Box 83, Folder 4)
    - Press clippings: Undated (no focus on specific project), circa 1980-2010 (Box 83, Folder 5)
  - Magazines, 1969-2010; 2.
    This subseries is comprised of full magazines that contain articles, reviews, photographs, or news items about or related to the work of George A. Romero.
    - Magazines, 1969 (Box 85, Folder 1)
      inter/VIEW Magazine 1, no. 4.
    - Magazines, 1970 (Box 85, Folder 2)
      Photon #19.
    - Magazines, 1971 (Box 85, Folder 3)
      Newsweek (November 8, 1971).
    - Magazines, 1972 (Box 85, Folder 4)
      Castle of Frankenstein #18 (3 copies).
    - Magazines, 1973 (Box 85, Folder 5)
      Films in Review (May 1973).
    - Magazines, 1976 (Box 85, Folder 6)
      Marble 4, no. 2 (March/April 1976) (15 copies), Fandom's Film Gallery #2 (April 1976) (2 copies).
    - Magazines, 1978 (Box 85, Folder 7)
      Cinefantastique 8, no. 1.
    - Magazines, 1979 (Box 85, Folder 8)
      The Gallery (July 1979). Includes first published version of Stephen King short story "The Crate" (later used in Creepshow).
    - Magazines, 1979 (Box 85, Folder 9)
      Film Comment (May-June 1979) (2 copies), Questar #5 (November 1979), Maclean's 92, no. 29 (July 1979) (2 copies), Rolling Stone #293 (June 1979), Cinema World 2, no. 2 (April 1979).
    - Magazines, 1980 (Box 86, Folder 1)
      Film Comment (March 1980), Screen International No. 7, New York (July 21 1980) (2 copies), Us (November 11, 1980), Today: The Inquirer Magazine (October 26, 1980).
    - Magazines, 1981 (Box 86, Folder 2)
      Pittsburgh Magazine (October 1981) (2 copies), In Cinema (March 1981), Film Comment (May-June 1981), Film Comment (July-Aug 1981), High Times (July 1981), Newsweek (April 13, 1981), Us (April 28, 1981), Heavy Metal (September 1981), Questar (October 1981), In Cinema (April/May 1981).
    - Magazines, 1982 (Box 86, Folder 3)